Guide to the Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files, 1892-1990 FFAL.002
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
- Multiple Artist Files, I.; 259 folders
  - Wil-Wind (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 252)
    Wilchusky, Le Ann Bartok; Wilde, John, 1919-2006; Wilder, Dorothy; Wilhelm, E. Paul; Wilke, Hannah; Williams, Gerald; Williams, Guy, 1932-2004; Williams, Hiram; Williams, Ralph, 1946-; Williams, Roger, 1943-; Williams, Wayne; Williams, Wheeler, 1897-1972; Williamson, Heidi Prescott; Willis, Jay; Willis, William, 1943-; Willson, Mary Ann, active 1810-1825; Wilson, Gahan; Wilson, Reginald; Wilson, Richard; Wilson, Sol; Wilt, Richard; Wind, Gerhard, 1928-
  - Wine-Woe (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 253)
    Winkler, John William, 1894-1979; Winn, Alice; Winter, Clark; Winter, Edward; Winter, Fritz, 1905-1976; Winter, Lumen Martin; Winter, Thelma Frazier; Wise, Vera; Witham, Vernon, 1925-; Wladyslaw, Anatol, 1913-2004; Wo, Henry Yue-Kee, 1927-; Woehrman, Ralph
  - Wof-Woq (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 254)
    Woiceske, Ronau William, 1887-1953; Wolfe, James, 1944-; Wood, Grant, 1891-1942; Wood, Howard; Wood, Steve; Woodham, Derrick; Woodruff, Thomas; Woodville, Richard Caton, 1856-1927; Woolley, Ellamarie; Woolley, Jackson; Wootton, John, approximately 1682-1764
  - Wor-Wz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 255)
    Worms, Jules, 1832-1924; Worner, Howard; Worner, Marysole; Worsing, Helen; Wray, Dick, 1933-; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959; Wright, Sylvia; Wukich, Richard; Wunderlich, Paul, 1927-2010; Wyatt, Benjamin Dean, 1775-1855; Wyatt, Benjamin I.; Wyeth, Henriette, 1907-1997; Wyeth, Jamie, 1946-; Wyzenbeck, David
  - X-Yos (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 256)
    Xceron, Jean, 1890-1967; Yamasaki, Minoru, 1912-1986; Yao, Qingzhang, 1941-; Yarde, Richard, 1939-; Yarnall, Agnes; Yasko, Rick; Yawor, Alex; Yellin, Samuel, 1885-1940; Yerxa, Thomas; Yokum, Kathi; Yoshida, Ray
  - Yot-Yz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 257)
    Young, David L.; Young, Joseph, 1919-2007; Young, Michael; Young, Tom, 1924-; Youngerman, Jack, 1926-; Youssef, Kamal, 1923-; Yunkers, Adja, 1900-1983
  - Za-Zie (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 258)
    Zachrisson, Julio, 1930-; Zadkine, Ossip; Zakharov, Gury; Zakin, Richard; Zammitt, Norman; Zandhuis, Jan; Zao, Wou-ki, 1920-2013; Zañartu, Enrique, 1921-2000; Zelmanoff, Marci; Zelt, Martie, 1930-; Zeng, Youhe, 1924-; Zepeda, Rafael, 1944-; Zerbe, Karl, 1903-1972; Zhang, Daqian, 1899-1983; Ziegler, Laura; Ziegler, Lee Woodward; Ziemann, Richard Claude
  - Zif-Zz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 259)
    Zim, Marco; Zimmer, Elli; Zimmerman, Paul; Zine, Mark; Zinner, Eloise Piper; Zocchi, Giuseppe, 1711-1767; Zogbé, Bibí, 1890-1975; Zoller, Edwin W., 1900-1967; Zollweg, Aileen Boules; Zorach, Marguerite, 1887-1968; Zorn, Anders, 1860-1920; Zox, Larry, 1937-2006; Zucker, Joe, 1941-; Zuloaga, Elisa; Zwart, Piet, 1885-1977; Zygler, Eleanor; Zúñiga, Francisco, 1912-1998
- Individual Artist Files, II.
  - Afro, 1912-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 260)
  - Albers, Josef (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 261)
  - Arms, John Taylor, 1887-1953 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 262)
  - Avery, Milton, 1885-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 263)
  - Baskin, Leonard, 1922-2000 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 264)
  - Beckmann, Max, 1884-1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 265)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1889-1975 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 266)
  - Beuys, Joseph (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 267)
  - Bott, Emil, 1827-1908 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 268)
  - Brunger, Thomas (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 269)
  - Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 270)
  - Cantini, Virgil (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 271-272)
  - Chagall, Marc, 1887-1985 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 273)
  - Cowles, Russell, 1887-1979 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 274)
  - Dalí, Salvador, 1904-1989 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 275)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, 1901-1985 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 276)
  - Duchamp, Marcel, 1887-1968 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 277)
  - Ernst, Max, 1891-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 278)
  - Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 279)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1928-2011 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 280)
  - Friedman, Ken, 1949- (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 281)
  - Hofmann, Hans, 1880-1966 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 282)
  - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 283)
  - Jenkins, Paul, 1923-2012 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 284)
  - Johns, Jasper, 1930- (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 285)
  - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 286)
  - Koerner, Henry, 1915-1991 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 287)
  - Kuhn, Walt, 1877-1949 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 288)
  - Le Clair, Charles (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 289)
  - Leonardo, da Vinci, 1452-1519 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 290)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1891-1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 291)
  - Lutz, Dan, 1906-1978 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 292)
  - Margo, Boris, 1902-1995 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 293)
  - Masson, André, 1896-1987 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 294)
  - Matisse, Henri, 1869-1954 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 295)
  - Moore, Henry, 1898-1986 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 296)
  - Motherwell, Robert (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 297)
  - Nama, George (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 298)
  - Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 299)
  - Noland, Kenneth, 1924-2010 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 300)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 301)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, 1929- (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 302)
  - Palmer, William, 1906-1987 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 303)
  - Pattison, Abbott L. (Abbott Lawrence), 1916-1999 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 304)
  - Paone, Peter, 1936- (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 305)
  - Papsdorf, Frederick, 1887-1978 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 306)
  - Pierce, Waldo (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 307)
  - Pereira, I. Rice (Irene Rice), 1902-1971 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 308)
  - Pershing, Louise (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 309)
  - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 310)
  - Pollock, Jackson, 1912-1956 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 311)
  - Price, Clayton S., 1874-1950 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 312)
  - Priebe, Karl J., 1914-1976 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 313)
  - Purinš, Girts, 1937- (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 314)
  - Rouault, Georges, 1871-1958 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 315)
  - Shahn, Ben, 1898-1969 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 316)
  - Smith, David, 1906-1965 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 317)
  - Tanner, Henry Ossawa, 1859-1937 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 318)
  - Trova, Ernest T., 1927-2009 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 319)
  - Vickery, Robert (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 320)
  - Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 321)
  - Weber, Max, 1881-1961 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 322)
  - Wengenroth, Stow, 1906-1978 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 323)
  - Whistler, James McNeill, 1834-1903 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 324)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1917-2009 (File-cabinet 2, Drawer 4, Folder 325)